♪If I am gone from this world,
will the dark night collapse?♪
♪If I never return
to guard by your side♪
♪If I seal away our encounter
and erase all trace♪
♪Like endless snow
falling into the deep sea♪
♪This life is but a fleeting illusion,
yet it gave me courage♪
♪Love is a miracle♪
=Spring Over Phoenix Pond=
(Adapted from Qin An'an's
"Spring Over Phoenix Pond")
=Episode 4=
(Marquis Yongping Residence)
In that case,
investigate this matter clearly
and clear my name.
You wretched servant.
How dare you frame others?
Speak.
Who put you up to this?
If you don't tell the truth,
I'll sell you off!
I didn't.
I really saw the Young Lady
with my own eyes
burying the doll.
His Highness is critically ill now
precisely because she cursed him!
You still won't tell the truth, huh?
- Stop.
- You...
- How dare you disobey!
Have you lost your mind?
You say I disobeyed?
Come with me and see
who is really framing whom.
How could there be such
a heartless mother in this world?
I was looking for a chance
to get close to her,
and this slap actually helped me out.
Jin,
rest assured.
I will make the butcher's daughter
move out of our house.
Open!
Weren't you dying?
You really colluded with Nanny Zhang
to harm your sister.
Spare me, Marquis.
Sister?
She's not my sister.
Father,
why does she get to come back?
Ever since she returned,
Jin even had to move out
of Mingyue Pavilion.
Jin was wronged so badly.
Absurd!
I did it all for Jin.
Why does she get to take away
everything that belongs to Jin?
I am protecting her.
I just like her.
Shut your mouth.
Shut up.
Get yourself to the study now.
Copy the family rules a hundred times!
Is no one going
to give me an explanation?
And you,
get out.
Mother,
please don't drive me away.
Please don't drive me away.
Jin,
do you think I want to do this?
If Prince Qi hadn't
fallen unconscious recently,
I would have proposed
a marriage for you by now.
But Zhao's marriage
with the Xiang family
cannot be ruined.
You must understand,
I can't disregard the future
of the Qi family just for your sake.
Jin,
don't worry.
I will send people to take care of you
and make sure you want for nothing.
So, Mother,
you don't want me anymore?
Be good.
Why?
It was Qi Zhao
who tampered with the sachet,
and it was also him
who used witchcraft to frame me.
Even if anyone had improper thoughts,
it was him toward me.
How dare you!
Don't you know what matters most
in this household?
Someone come.
Take her away.
- Yes, Madam.
- (For Zhao's marriage with the Xiangs,)
- Move.
(I can never let you stay.)
(Mingyue Pavilion)
Young Lady,
this is the ointment sent to you
by Prince Jing's men.
This slap actually helped me out.
I was looking
for a chance to get close to her.
Go to our manor and fetch
a jar of Yulong Ointment,
and then give it to the Young Lady.
I heard Miss Jin has been kicked out.
That's wonderful.
From now on, Mingyue Pavilion
belongs to you, Young Lady.
Yuan...
Father, what brings you here?
I came to check on you.
Here is the thing, Yuan.
Now that you've returned home,
I
would like to hold
a grand welcome ceremony for you.
However, regarding this ceremony...
Father,
please feel free to speak directly.
Actually, this is Prince Jing's idea.
Prince Jing learned
that you are close
with the Eldest Princess,
so he wants to use this ceremony
to invite Her Highness down the mountain
to meet with friends and relatives.
Besides,
the Eldest Princess's presence
would bring great honor
to the Qi family as well.
Rest assured, Father.
I will surely invite
the Eldest Princess.
That's wonderful.
Good.
Then, it's settled.
It's settled, then.
By the way,
tomorrow,
the noble ladies of the capital
will go to Guanyin Temple to pray.
You should go along with them
and make an appearance in public.
(Prince Jing,)
(what a clever move.)
Why are you here?
Your Highness sent ointment first,
then forced me to agree
to invite the Eldest Princess.
Didn't you just want me to come see you?
You don't know the Eldest Princess,
yet you used my name
to boost your own status.
That is hardly the conduct
of a virtuous person.
I simply disliked it
and intentionally exposed you.
Your Highness saw today
how the Qi family treats me, too.
What I did
was merely for self-preservation.
The banquet is in just three days.
Marquis Yongping seemed so eager.
He has probably
already sent out the invitations.
The entire capital
is waiting for
the Eldest Princess to arrive.
Young Lady Qi,
how will you clean up this mess?
If I fail to bring her,
I will be thrown out of the house.
Unless
Your Highness helps me.
Your predicament
is indeed pitiful.
But what does that have to do with me?
If I help you,
what benefit is there for me?
♪Leaves fall in the cold wind,
a fleeting glance between pavilions♪
♪Love drifts through the whirlpool
of farewell, brushing past me♪
♪Only longing
leaves me wounded all over♪
♪Yet I still fear you'll forget me♪
♪If I am gone from this world,
will the dark night collapse?♪
♪If I never return
to guard by your side♪
♪This love defies fate,
holding my breath♪
♪To kiss your eyes♪
♪I'd cross seas and lands♪
♪To change an uncertain fate,
never part again♪
♪If I seal away our encounter
and erase all trace♪
♪Like endless snow
falling into the deep sea♪
♪This life is but a fleeting illusion,
yet it gave me courage♪
♪Love is a miracle♪
♪This love defies fate♪
♪To change an uncertain fate,
never part again♪
♪If I seal away our encounter♪
♪Yet it gave me courage♪
♪Love is a miracle♪